parasoft.com 2017-03-03

# Online Information Privacy Policy - Parasoft

At Parasoft we are committed to protecting your personal information that you share with us through forms, surveys and inquiries on our web site, in our e-mail messages and web promotions.

This statement outlines our privacy policy regarding any information you provide to us through the use of registration forms, surveys, inquiries, responses to e-mail as well as data collected from web based promotions.

Parasoft Corporation collects the following information: 

  * IP addresses
  * browsers in use data
  * information stored in cookies
  * information you provide through the submission of forms, surveys, and e-mail response and web promotion responses

Common non-personalized information - as to visitors IP addresses and the type of browsers in use by our readers, viewers, and customers are automatically logged and is used by Parasoft Corporation for common web traffic data reports and is considered by Parasoft Corporation to be non-personal in nature.

**The Use of Cookies:**

Parasoft may use cookies to collect non-personal information for the purpose of providing a more personalized experience and faster return access for our customers, prospective customers and all visitors alike. You may choose to disable all cookies or have your browser warn you each time that a request to place a cookie is being made. If you disable cookies (or refuse to accept a cookie), you may be required to repeat the log on procedure each time you attempt to enter specific areas where unique identifier information is required.

Parasoft Corporation may trade or share such personal and/or company specific contact information for use by third parties who offer complementary/revelant products or services, where authorized or required by law, or unless you have submitted a written request denying such use of personal and/or company specific contact information.

Prospective customers and persons seeking general information about Parasoft and Parasoft products can visit the informational portion of parasoft.com without the requirement of providing personal and/or company specific contact information to us. To download Parasoft software for evaluation or for purchase, and to gain access to customer specific information or programs, you may be required to provide certain personal and/or company specific contact information (such as your name, company name, telephone and e-mail address). In addition to registration requirements for entry into the customer download and information portions of parasoft.com any activities such as purchasing software or support, will require the collection of additional personal and/or company specific contact information such as company shipping receiving addresses and credit card number with required street and billing addresses as applicable.

Parasoft Corporation reserves the right to disclose such personal and/or company specific contact information, without notice, if we believe that such action is necessary to defend and protect the rights or property of Parasoft Corporation and its subsidiaries.

**Credit Card Information**

If your credit card number is used to process your request for products or services it is Parasoft Corporation policy that it will not be shared with third parties that are not involved with the transaction.

**Part II - How Parasoft Corporation Uses the Information Gathered**

Parasoft Corporation uses the information that you provide for these purposes: 

  * To provide the products, services or customer benefits and programs designed specifically to enhance your customer satisfaction.
  * To ensure proper billing on any online transactions.
  * To measure customer demand or interest in various offerings and promotions.
  * For internal marketing, promotional research and marketing metrics tracking.

Parasoft Corporation uses the information gathered in an effort to provide you with information about new products and services as well as upgrades and notification about other Parasoft products that Parasoft Corporation believes are beneficial to you as Parasoft customer.

**Protecting Your Privacy**

Parasoft.com and parasoft electronic mail systems sometimes provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information from you. You should always have the option of removing your name from our e-mail mailing list(s) so that you will not receive further e-mail promotional communications from us.

In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, it is best to follow the specific instructions outlined within the communications you receive from us. If you are unable to complete the process indicated in such communications, send Parasoft Corporation an e-mail. If you are sent an e-mail from Parasoft Corporation without the required option to be removed from the current e-mail list and thereby be removed from future mailings. Contact Parasoft Corporation by e-mail, writing or phone, so we may correct the situation immediately.

Unfortunately, no one can guarantee that data transmitted over the Internet will be secure at any point during the transmission. Due to the nature of electronic information transmission we can only strive to protect your personal and/or company specific contact information. Parasoft Corporation cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from any forms required to download our products or to engage or request engagement into any of our online customer services, you therefore do so - at your own risk. Upon receipt of your transmission, we strive to ensure the security of that information within our internal systems at all times.

**Parasoft Privacy Policy Updates**

By using parasoft.com, you signify your acceptance of this privacy policy. Parasoft Corporation reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time.

Visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time to stay abreast of any changes. Your continued use of parasoft.com - following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept those changes.

**Questions or Comments?**

If you have any further questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please send us an [e-mail](mailto:info@parasoft.com).

Parasoft Corporation Online Information Privacy Policy – Modified August 9, 2002.
